





















**Figma** 

Sketch

ceros



Illustrator After Effects

ceros

WordPress

# ABOUT ME 偷

I'm a creative and engagement-driven digital designer for web, apps and social media platforms. I think of design as journeys that work with content to optimize experiences in using critical design thinking and research, whether it's in UX/UI or in digital visuals. As a designer, I also know when and how to work with prompt engineering and AI tools to enhance designs.

I'm able to create designs tailored for phones, tablets to large monitors. I have experience with layouts, graphics, product mapping, wireframes, typography and colour.

## **EDUCATION**

Mar 2017 - Jun 2017 General Assembly (formerly Bitmaker)

Web Development **Program** 

> Web Development Immersive progam

Jan 2001 - Aug 2001 **Birmingham City University** 

# UK exchange design course

> UK exchange program selected by Toronto Metropolitan University to partake in Birmingham

1998 1999 2000 2001 2002

Aug 2000 **UAL: Central Saint Martins** 

#### **Experimentational Design Course**

> Experimentational design course using unconventional materials and concepts

Sep 1998 - Apr 2002 Toronto Metropolitan University (formerly Ryerson University)

2017

#### B.A.A. - Fashion Design Degree

> Fashion Design, Fashion Marketing, Consumer Product Design, some Graphic Design

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

with earlier experiences on LinkedIn



# Senior Designer, Digital & Multimedia • Borden Ladner Gervais LLP • Jan 2020 - Feb 2024

> Creating concepts, visuals and digital products for <u>BLG</u> and subsidiary legal services <u>BLG Beyond</u>; webpages, apps to social media platform visuals; balancing quality, speed, accuracry and consistency in brand standards and goals; Acted as BLG Affinity group committee member (2021 - 2023)



#### Digital Designer • Blake, Cassels & Graydon LLP • Aug 2017 - Jan 2020

> Creating digital assets for launch of blakes.com, landing pages, client-facing marketing materials, internal communications, social media channels, print materials



#### Design Manager, Consumer Products • Thinkway Toys • Apr 2016 - Mar 2017

> Design Manager in licensed consumer products including Lucas Films Ltd. (Star Wars Rogue One), ©Disney/Pixar (Cars 3), Universal Studios (Despicable Me 3)



### Associate, Online Product Approval • Disney Consumer Products (Disney Canada) • Nov 2013 - Mar 2016

- > Creative associate as part of Disney Canada in the OPA team for consumer softlines and hardllines products sold across Canada; including stores such as Walmart Canada and Canadian Tire,
- > Working with team in guiding 50+ licensees on 500+ products seasonally including ©Disney/Pixar and Frozen. Managing online product design approvals and meeting with vendors & licensees on communicating design goals and brand guides to defining brand initiatives

DOLCE & GABBANA

## Associate • Dolce & Gabbana (Milan, Italy) • Feb 2013 - Sept 2013

> Brought 10 years of Canadian design experience abroad and resulted in an opportunity for Dolce & Gabbana in Milan; preparation and assistance on Fall 2013 and Spring 2014 RTW collections, creation of look books